Savage pursuit in the wilderness!
Death Hunt is a action, adventure, western film directed by Peter R. Hunt.
Yukon Territory, Canada, November 1931.
Albert Johnson, a trapper who lives alone in the mountains, buys a dog almost dead
after a brutal dogfight, a good deed that will put him in trouble.
Albert Johnson, played by Charles Bronson.
RCMP Sgt. Edgar Millen, played by Lee Marvin.
RCMP Const. Alvin Adams, played by Andrew Stevens.
George Washington Lincoln 'Sundog' Brown, played by Carl Weathers.
Hazel, played by Ed Lauter.
RCAF Pilot Capt. Hank Tucker, played by Scott Hylands.
Death Hunt is a 1981 Western action film directed by Peter Hunt.
The film stars Charles Bronson, Lee Marvin, Angie Dickinson, Carl
Weathers, Maury Chaykin, Ed Lauter and Andrew Stevens.
Death Hunt was a fictionalized account of the Royal Canadian Mounted
Police (RCMP) pursuit of a man named Albert Johnson.
Earlier films exploring the same topic were The Mad Trapper (1972),  a British made-for-television
production and Challenge to Be Free (also known as Mad Trapper of the Yukon and Mad Trapper) (1975).
The film explores themes of new year's eve, canada,
bounty hunter, husky, based on true story.
The tone is dark.